CURRICULAM-VITAE

Correspondence Address S/O :- Sri Nagesh Dutt Pathak.

Dist:- Simdega

State:- Jharkhand

Call:- 9334929263

Shidheshwar Pathak

Email: - Shidhu.pathak@Gmail.Com

Objective: Seeking a challenging assignment in Technical Support/Networking Administration/System Administration with a leading organisation

OVERVIEW

Customer Service, Network Troubleshooting Maintenance & server Administration.

Current Profile: -

Total Years of Experience : 10 years

Current Industry : IT-Hardware/Networking/system & remote administration

Old preference : bokaro steel plant,[bokaro] Hindustan times . co pvt. Ltd Ranchi,

Current Location : Jharkhand (district transport office simdega)

Experience: -

Pcs Technology L.t.d (11 FUB 2008 TO NOVEM 2009)

Designation: -- Customer Support Engineer

CMS Info Computer pvt.Ltd .Kolkata (JAN 2010 to 4th April 2010)

Designation :-- Customer Support Engineer

Eye global technology pvt. Ltd Mumbai 1st Novem 2010 to till date

Designation: -- data entry operator

Areas of Expertise (Things which I am best at):

- ❖ INSTALLATION AND CONFIGRATION OF DIFFERENCE TYPE OF O/S
- ❖ O/S -WIN 98,WIN XP.WIN VISTA. WIN 7, WIN 8 REDHAT (LINUX), UBUNTU
- ❖ SERVER 2000,& SERVER 2003 WITH RAID
- ❖ SOL SERVER 2000, ORACLE 10G.
- ❖ INSTALLATION AND CONFIGRATION OF VXL TERMSERVER TS 3010
- ❖ MAIL CONFIGRATION OF MICROSOFT OUTLOOK, AND OUTLOOK EXPRESS.
- ❖ LOTUS MAIL CONFIGRATION AND TROUBLESHOOTING.MANAGING REGIONAL LOCAL USERS &JOINING THEM ON its INTERNET DOMIN.
- ❖ INSTALLATION AND TROUBLESHOOTING OF PRINTER, AS LIKE TVSE MSP 335, DMP, TALLY T2250, LIPI LINE PRINTER T300, PASSBOOK PRINTER PR2E, PRINTROINX, 7000, TVS 10000 DMP LINE PRINTER, HP LASERJET 1010, 1020, 4050, 1160, DESKJET, HP DMP LINE PRINTER 8000, 5000 etc

Networking:-

- ➤ LAN, CAN, WAN WIRELES NETWORKING WITH (WI FI) DIVICE,
- > TRUBLESHOOTING OF NETWORKING PROBLEM

Job Profile:-

- ❖ Managing & troubleshooting of hp Unix server hprp 5470 with cluster, risc server and oracle application server environment with hp autoloader 448, under bokaro steel plant, installation, testing and Maintenance of Hardware parts & LAN etc. installation configuration and troubleshooting of VXL term server.
- ❖ Managing 6 Branch of LIC OF INDIA. Handling Linux environment, installation, testing and Maintenance of Hardware parts & network troubleshooting etc. Supervising the PC in LAN environment. Managing and troubleshooting of workstations & ensuring uninterrupted smooth running of Computers.
- ❖ Installation, troubleshooting and Maintenance of printer as like TVSE MSP335, DMP. Tally t2250, Lip line printer t300, passbook printer pr2e, Printronix 7000, TVS 10000 DMP line printer, Hp LaserJet 1010,1020, 1160, desk jet hp 8000N, Hp 5000 hp etc.
- Central Marketing Organization (SRM) Bokaro steel city Working under WIN 98, XP.WIN VSTA, UNIX. Outlook express configuration & troubleshooting of networking problem
- Managing 16 Branch bank of India and 6 anther bank location under customer engineer In bokaro steel city.
- FMS backup support Engineer at united India corporation of india ltd regional branch bokaro, steel city
- ❖ FMS backup support Engineer at Hindustan times co PVT LTD Ranchi Jharkhand
- ❖ Data entry operator at district transport office simdega under vahan & sarathi software making the driving licence dl data fitting , vehicle registration , taxation and & its related working Hindi and English typing vahan & sarathi software installation etc

Technical Knowledge: -

Course Name- Advance PC+ Net from Indian Institute of Hardware Technology (IIHT, Ranchi)

Semester	Topic	Duration of Course
Electronic	Analog and Digital	January 2004 to June 2004
Hardware	System Assembling, Monitor, SMPS, CD Drive, FDD, KBD, Mouse and Peripheral (DMP, Laser Inkjet	July 2004 to October2004
Software	Ms office	November 2004 to December 2004
Networking	LAN, WAN, MAN	February 2005 to June 2005
MCSE	WIN XP, Server 2000, Advance Server 2000, 2003, Active Directory Environment	March 2006 to August 2006
CCNA	Basics of two router connecting router with using different type of Protocol, IP add and Subnet Masking etc	August 2006 to November 2006
Red Hat (Linux)	Installing Trouble Shooting, Make LAN Set up with Red Hat	March 2007 to June 2007
SQL Server	Data Entry Trouble Shooting etc.	July 2007
Warless Networking	LAN with (WI-FI)	August 2007

DCA from pioneer computer centre simdega

Academic Qualification:-

> : Matriculation from **JSEB** (RANCHI) in 2000

> : Intermediate (Isc from **JAC** (RANCHI) in 2004

> : BCA continue from Sikkim manipal univercity

Languages:

Languages	Read	Write	Speak	Understand
Hindi	Yes	Yes	Yes	Yes
English	Yes	Yes	Yes	Yes

Personal Profile :-

Father's Name	: -	Sri nagesh dutt pathak	
Date of Birth	: -	26 th March 1984	
Nationality	:-	Indian	
Martial status	:-	Single	
Gender	:-	Male	
Hobbies	:-	Listening to music	
		formation furnished above are true and correct to the best of always try to abide by them.	of my
Date:			
Place		Sign	nature: